grantwritingexpress.com 2007-08-24

# Grant Writing Express Terms & Conditions

This Privacy Policy describes the terms of our commitment to your privacy. At Grant Writing Express and GrantWritingExpress.com we take privacy and data protection issues seriously. We have designed this Privacy Policy to explain how we handle your personally identifiable information collected by Grant Writing Express or our merchant account service provider (Frontline), when you register to access and/or purchase our Grant Writing Express publication and submit your personally identifiable information through GrantWritingExpress.com.com using Frontline, or use another credit card provider 

As GrantWritingExpress.com grows and expands, we may revise this policy, so please check back frequently. 

Your use of this site is evidence of your acceptance of the terms this Privacy Policy and your agreement to check our Privacy Policy each time you visit the site for any changes

I. Scope of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers Grant Writing Express’s treatment of personally identifiable information that you provide us as a User of our GrantWritingExpress.com web site services, as well as your personally identifiable consumer information that we acquire in the course of our business. It also covers our treatment of personally identifiable information that our business partners may share with us.

Our Commitment to You

This policy describes our privacy practices with respect to current and former users of this web site. It will help you understand what information we collect, when and how we share it. 

At GrantWritingExpress.com we recognize the importance of maintaining and protecting your privacy and the privacy of your personal information. The personally identifiable information you provide us when you visit or use our web site to review or purchase our publication Grant Writing Express © 2007 may include your personal information which is protected by federal and state privacy laws. We are also aware of widespread consumer concerns about identity theft and related privacy issues.

In light of these laws and your rightful concerns about privacy we have established this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to protect your privacy rights when you use this GrantWritingExpress.com web site.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact us by e-mail using our Secure Contact Form or by phone at (702) 942-1762. 

II. Personal Identifiable Information We Collect and Use

We collect personally identifiable information when you visit this GrantWritingExpress.com web site and when you purchase Grant Writing Express publication from this web site. We may also receive personally identifiable information from our resellers and other business partners.

We ask for your contact information, including your name, street address, e-mail address, phone number, when you register to access Grant Writing Express. You also submit personal financial information such as a bank account and/or credit card number to Frontline or other credit card ask for you when you purchase our publication, Grant Writing Express. You submit other personal information to us when you use our web site including Internet cookies, which are described below. 

We use the services of Frontline as our merchant service account provider to process your payment transactions. Grant Writing Express is not and cannot be responsible for the privacy policies of Frontline, any other third party payment processor, or any other payment or credit card provider that you may use. We typically receive information related to the transaction from Frontline. This typically includes information about the payment you as a consumer have provided to Frontline or other credit card when you purchase Grant Writing Express.

We suggest and encourage you to review Frontline’s Privacy Policy before you use their services, as the information you provide to Frontline typically includes your personally identifiable financial information and Frontline will typically use and reuse the information to fulfill your requests for our publication, process payment transactions, billing, and other payment processing services associated with your purchase transaction. 

We may also send merchant service announcements and other periodic notices about specials and new publications or services to you as our customer or user of GrantWritingExpress.com. You have the right to “opt-out” of this e-mail notice system at using our Unsubscribe Form.

Children: Grant Writing Express, through this GrantWritingExpress.com web site, does not offer services, sell products or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children, defined herein as anyone under the age of 16. 

III. How We Use Personal Information You Submit to Our Website

Any personally identifiable information you provide to a payment processor is used to process payment transactions and for no other purpose. 

Our GrantWritingExpress.com web site provides you the opportunity to read Grant Writing Express on-line, to educate and inform you about the grant industry and how to obtain grants. 

We collect personal data from many different sources: 

o From you over the Internet;  
o From agents or service providers, including service providers who conduct marketing service for us;  
o From the forms you submit to us to purchase Grant Writing Express  
o From any other forms or information you submit using our merchant account service provider, Frontline; and  
o Other data providers.

We may disclose your personally identifiable data we collect to: 

o Service providers used to maintain your policy, process your transaction or that assist us with processing payments;  
o Service providers that perform marketing services for us;  
o A court or governmental agency when there is a lawful request;  
o Assist law enforcement and prevent criminal activity and/or fraud;  
o As otherwise allowed or required by law.

IV. Information Sharing and Disclosure

We share and disclose such information only as described below:

Grant Writing Express and/or GrantWritingExpress.com will share & transfer personally identifiable information about you to other third parties.

If you have any questions about how we use your personal information, you should contact us directly and immediately. If you have any questions about how another party (such as a payment processing vendor bank or bank) with whom we you do business handles your personal information, you should contact that company directly and immediately. 

Log Files

We use your computer’s IP address to analyze trends, administer the site, track the users’ movement, and gather broad demographic information (for aggregate use). Your IP address is never linked to your personally identifiable information.

Cookies

A cookie is a data stored on the your (user’s) computer that is tied to information about the you, our web site “User”.

If you purchase Grant Writing Express at this GrantWritingExpress.com site, you will likely provide personally identifiable information that will include Internet cookies, which help our Internet application process but we do not store such personal information. 

Our use of cookies is in not linked to any personally identifiable information you provide about yourself while visiting and using this GrantWritingExpress.com web site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. 

Information Obtained from ‘Cookies’

Many websites, including this one, collect information about your computer, your email address, your IP address. You must assume that your web-viewing or web-use activity is monitored, tracked, and information collected. This information is not usually of a personal nature, but it may help define your viewing habits and product preferences even though the website may or may not have any idea who you are.

"Cookies" is web jargon for bits of computer code placed on your hard drive. A cookie is a data stored on the your (user’s) computer that is tied to information about the you, our web site “User”. Websites use this to keep you 'logged in', to keep track of search criteria, to monitor use, to password protect use of the site or use of products sold by the site. Cookies can also be used to obtain information about your computer configuration or your use of your computer.

Cookies can be used to electronically gather information about you. Again, it may or may not be personal information, but it is information and by using this site you are expressly giving permission to use 'cookies' and to use the information gathered from their use to benefit you. You also give permission to collect, archive, retrieve, and use any information collected for product design, product offers to you, and general commercial solicitation purposes by this site or joint venture partners, affiliates, and marketing organizations.

Grant Writing Express may share aggregated statistical information such as website traffic or demographic information with our business partners. In no case will your personally identifiable information be included in such aggregated information.

V. About the Personal Information We Collect and How It is Used

We collect and obtain information about our Users and customers in various ways, such as: 

o Information you provide when you purchase Grant Writing Express from our web site and provide your personal credit card and other personal and financial information to Frontline.

o Online ordering via SSL encrypted communication provided by Frontline when accepting your purchase order using a credit card, provides information to us but does not provide complete credit card numbers. In the process of online ordering, as a purchaser you provide your name, address, city, state, email address, phone number, CVV2 (back of card) number, and, occasionally a member password. You should consider all this information available to the website.

o You email inquiries: Users who wish to communicate with the website do so under two conditions: 1) you give your permission to be contacted directly by us at GrantWritingExpress.com; and 2) you understand that you are subject to any ‘submission’ provisions of our Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy. While your email address may or may not be used to solicit you, it is added to this GrantWritingExpress.com web site's general solicitation database.

o User email or testimonials: If you send us an email at this GrantWritingExpress.com website, or if you communicate with us by phone or mail, we collect information about your communication. By communicating with us at GrantWritingExpress.com you give your permission for us to collect, archive, retrieve, and otherwise use any information collected as we see fit in Grant Writing Express Inc.’s sole discretion.

o Users clicking on web site banners, popups or other forms of web site advertising: If you click on banners, pop-ups or hyperlinked advertising appearing on this GrantWritingExpress.com website, you must assume that information is being collected about you at that time. Because these are advertisements provided by third parties, Grant Writing Express is not responsible for the use of information collected in such a fashion by such third part advertisers.

User understands, acknowledges and agrees: 

(1) that information will be collected, 

(2) that ‘cookies’ will usually be placed on their hard drive,

(3) that Grant Writing Express and this GrantWritingExpress.com website does not have any control over what happens with this information, 

(4) that Grant Writing Express and GrantWritingExpress.com take no responsibility over the accuracy or content of such advertisements, 

(5) that Grant Writing Express and GrantWritingExpress.com are not responsible for downloads from third party advertisers that contain viruses or worms or other computer code that causes their computer or software harm, and 

6) that Grant Writing Express and GrantWritingExpress.com assume no responsibility for any data that is garnered from the click itself or that the advertiser collects. 

o Information obtained from referring email or third party web sites

1) If you send a friend an email from this GrantWritingExpress.com site or if you send the url or one of our web pages to a friend, you must assume that some data is collected about your IP address or your email address and that of your friend. You must assume that referred emails or web pages may appear to come from your email. 

2) User acknowledges and accepts full responsibility for referring pages or email to a friend and agree to indemnify Grant Writing Express for any damage, intentional or unintentional that results from said referrals. (see Limited Liability provisions #12-13 in our Terms of Service Agreement.)

VI. Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy will continually change, so you should not assume that it will remain the same. Grant Writing Express and GrantWritingExpress.com reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. 

In the event of a material change to this privacy policy and how Grant Writing Express will use personally identifiable information, we will post notices of such material change on the home page of this GrantWritingExpress.com web site prior to implementing such change. If you have additional questions about this Policy, please contact us using our Secure Contact Form.

Notice of Changes

As our GrantWritingExpress.com services evolve and expand, we may modify, revise or amend this policy, at any time and for any reason, so please check back frequently. We encourage you to periodically check this Privacy Policy for any changes or updates. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this web site. If you have questions about GrantWritingExpress.com privacy practices please contact us directly at 

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this web site using our Secure Contact Form

All users of this GrantWritingExpress.com web site and our services should periodically check this posted Privacy Policy for any changes or updates.

Changes to this Privacy Policy without notice

Unless, in the sole opinion of Grant Writing Express, this policy changes so drastically as to suggest a posted notification on the site or via email, you will not receive notification of changes to this Privacy Policy. We do not, under any circumstances, promise such notification of changes to this Privacy Policy.

VII. Links to other Websites

This Privacy Policy applies only to this GrantWritingExpress.com web site. It does not apply to third parties such as other companies, organizations, or entities to which Grant Writing Express and this GrantWritingExpress.com web site links but does not own or control.

As stated in disclaimers throughout Grant Writing Express and in this GrantWritingExpress.com site’s Terms of Service, Grant Writing Express contains links to third party web sites and specific web pages on third party web sites that are not under our control. Each of these third party websites has its own privacy policies. Grant Writing Express is not responsible for the privacy policies, practices or content of these third party web sites. Each linked site was visited prior to linking to review its content for Grant Writing Express. However, we cannot control the privacy policies or any changes in privacy policies, of any third parties. Consequently, for your own protection, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of third party sites after you access them by linking from Grant Writing Express to make sure that they respect your privacy.

VIII. Your Right to Review and Correct Your Personal Data

You have a right to review your personal data. To do so please contact us by e-mail using our Secure Contact Form or by phone at (702) 942-1762. Please include your name, e-mail address, and identify the kind of information you wish to obtain. 

Correcting or Updating Your Personal Information

Contact Form.This GrantWritingExpress.com site gives users the following options for changing and modifying any personal information about yourself that you have previously provided to us on this GrantWritingExpress.com web site. Please send us an e-mail using our 

Correcting Errors

If you find an error, let us know and we will review it. If we agree, we will correct our files. If we disagree, you may file a short statement of dispute with us. Your statement will be included with any information we disclose in the future. You can also request that we send it to anyone who received your information from us in the past two years.

IX. Questions, Comments, Complaints or Incident Reports

If you have questions about GrantWritingExpress.com privacy practices please contact us using our Contact Form.
